[
  { "question": "cold, colder",
    "answer": "the coldest",
    "success": "0",
    "failure": "0",
    "type": "adjectives"
  },
  { "question": "warm, warmer",
    "answer": "the warmest",
    "success": "0",
    "failure": "0",
    "type": "adjectives"
  },
  { "question": "big, bigger",
    "answer": "the biggest",
    "success": "0",
    "failure": "0",
    "type": "adjectives"
  },
  { "question": "Я",
    "answer": "i",
    "success": "0",
    "failure": "0",
    "type": "translate"
  },
  { "question": "Ты",
    "answer": "you",
    "success": "0",
    "failure": "0",
    "type": "translate"
  },
  { "question": "Мы",
    "answer": "we",
    "success": "0",
    "failure": "0",
    "type": "translate"
  },

  { "question": "I play",
    "answer": "Present Simple",
    "success": "0",
    "failure": "0",
    "type": "tenses"
  },
  { "question": "I played",
    "answer": "Past Simple",
    "success": "0",
    "failure": "0",
    "type": "tenses"
  },
  { "question": "I shall play",
    "answer": "Future Simple",
    "success": "0",
    "failure": "0",
    "type": "tenses"
  },

  { "question": "I am playing",
    "answer": "Present Continuous",
    "success": "0",
    "failure": "0",
    "type": "tenses"
  },
  { "question": "I was playing",
    "answer": "Past Continuous",
    "success": "0",
    "failure": "0",
    "type": "tenses"
  },
  { "question": "I shall be playing",
    "answer": "Future Continuous",
    "success": "0",
    "failure": "0",
    "type": "tenses"
  },

  { "question": "I have played",
    "answer": "Present Perfect",
    "success": "0",
    "failure": "0",
    "type": "tenses"
  },
  { "question": "I had played",
    "answer": "Past Perfect",
    "success": "0",
    "failure": "0",
    "type": "tenses"
  },
  { "question": "I shall have played",
    "answer": "Future Perfect",
    "success": "0",
    "failure": "0",
    "type": "tenses"
  },

  { "question": "I have been playing",
    "answer": "Present Perfect Continuous",
    "success": "0",
    "failure": "0",
    "type": "tenses"
  },
  { "question": "I had been playing",
    "answer": "Past Perfect Continuous",
    "success": "0",
    "failure": "0",
    "type": "tenses"
  },
  { "question": "I shall have been playing",
    "answer": "Future Perfect Continuous",
    "success": "0",
    "failure": "0",
    "type": "tenses"
  }
]
